# Răzvan Ritivoi

Sibiu, Romania



razvanritivoi1996@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/r%C4%83zvan-ritivoi-39646a226

# Summary

In addition to my work as a Python Software Developer at Visma, I am also currently a student in my third year of computer science studies at Lucian Blaga University of Sibiu. This combination of professional experience and formal education has given me a well-rounded foundation in computer science and has allowed me to hone my skills in both theory and practice.

As a Python Software Developer, I have gained extensive experience in system engineering and software development, particularly in the realm of Cloud Computing and Automation. I have gained a deep understanding of Python, and have applied it to various projects and tasks.

I am passionate about continuing to learn and grow as a Software Developer, and I am excited to apply the knowledge and skills from my work and studies to future projects.

# **Experience**



### Nython Developer

Visma

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 2 months)



Visma

Jul 2021 - Jan 2022 (7 months)

#### **Education**



## Lucian Blaga University of Sibiu

Engineer's degree, Computer Science Sep 2020 - Jul 2024

#### 🔝 National College "Onisifor Ghibu"

Baccalaureate diploma, Mathematics and Computer Science Sep 2016 - Jul 2020

#### **Licenses & Certifications**



PCEP-30-02 - Python Institute

ocqX.pXuq.rwe7

- **European Computer Driving Licence ECDL** ECDL ROMANIA
- © Certificate of Professional Competence in IT Ministerul Educației Naționale

# **Skills**

Python (Programming Language) • REST APIs • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Django • Docker • Software Development • Git • Infrastructure as code (IaC) • Google Cloud Platform (GCP)